      Afghanistan
is a landlocked country located between the borders of Central and South Asia. <br>
Afghanistan is a majority Muslim country, with 99.7% of its population being Muslim, and 0.3% belonging to other religions. <br>
The capital of Afghanistan, and also its most populous city, is Kabul. <br>
The official languages of Afghanistan are Dari, or Dari Persian,  and Pashto. <br>
The total area of Afghanistan is 652,230 square kilometres (or 251,830 square miles) <br>
The total population of Afghanistan (as of 2019) is 32,225,560, with a density of 46 people/kilometre (119.1/square mile). <br>
The official currency of Afghanistan is the Afghan Afghani. <br>
