Albania
is a country in southwestern Europe, located in the Balkan region. <br>
Albania has no official religion, but 58.79% of Albanias population is Muslim, with Christianity coming in second at 16.99%. <br>
Tirana is the capital of Albania, as well as its largest city. <br>
The official language of Albania is Albanian, with Greek, Aromanian, and Macedonian being recognised minority languages. <br>
The total area of Albania is 28,748 square kilometres (11,100 square miles), with roughly 4.7% of area being water. <br>
Albanias total population (as of 2020) is 2,845,955, with a density of 98 people/kilometre (253.8/square mile). <br>
The official currency of Albania is the Albanian Lek. <br>